Finding Aid to the AIDS History Project — Ephemera Collection, 1973, 1981-2002 MSS.2000.31
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
- Posters and Oversized Items, 1981-2002; Series 2; Box 4 and Map Case: 69 items
  - Large Oversize Posters and Ephemera
    - English language: USA/English Canada (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - "Play Safe This Summer." AIDS Vancouver. Illustrated poster of two shirtless men in jeans with giant safety pin behind them. © art by Djaef? (2 copies), ca 1986. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 23)
      - "Rubbers are Bringing Men Together Again." Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Hotline, NYC. Photo by Naakkve. © GMHC., ca 1986. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 24)
      - "Football can be risky without Protection… So Can Sex." © Hawaii Planned Parenthood. Photo by Ric Noyle. (2 copies)., ca 1986. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 25)
      - "Show The World This Can't Go On." The International Display of the entire NAMES Project AIDS Memorial Quilt. Design by Pam Nishikawa., ca October 9 - 11, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 26)
      - "Keep Your Sex Life Alive. AIDS is a Killer. Use a Condom." Photo by Jerry LaRocca. © 1988 Turtledove Clemens Inc. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 27)
      - "Power: Strength Through Diversity" Series, b/w poster, copyright Steel Creek Studio, Inc., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 28)
      - "This is How You Can Get AIDS." Philadelphia Department of Public Health. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 29)
      - "Look at who can get AIDS. Protect Yourself, Use a Condom." Mirrored square on the poster. Philadelphia Department of Public Health. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 3, Item 30)
    - European: The Netherlands, Germany, Switzerland, Denmark. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - " Vrouwen en AIDS." Dutch Language. Lezingen workshops. World AIDS Day Symposium. The Netherlands. December 1, 1990., ca December 1, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - "Gebruik Altijd condooms!" Praliseri AIDS, SDOS. (Blue version). The Netherlands., ca 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - "Vrij veilig! Gebruik altijd condooms." Praliseri AIDS, SDOS. (Green version). The Netherlands., ca 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - "Zuid-Afrika. Dragers can het AIDS virus. Ver van uwbed?" AIDS Fonds. The Netherlands. 1990s., ca 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - "AIDS – infolijn gratis." AIDS Fonds. The Netherlands, 1997., ca 1997. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - "Alrededor del mundo." Spanish Language. Proyecto Sectorial: Prevencion y Control del SIDA en Paises en Desarrollo. Germany, 1999., ca 1999. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - "Je weg of loop je loop mee. I Juni 1997." Dutch Language. Walk for Life, AIDS Fonds. The Netherlands., ca 1997. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - "Universal precautions to prevent infection with HIV when assisting at childbirth." World Health Organization (WHO), Maternal Health & Safe Motherhood programme, Division of Family Health. Switzerland, 1995., ca 1995. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - "175 Kein Anschlub unter dieser nummer." German Language. AIDS Hilfe e.v. Germany. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - "A Global View of HIV infection." UNAIDS, AIDS feedback, Institute for Social and Preventative Medicine, University of Zurich. Switzerland, 1995., ca 1995. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - "Safe Motherhood." World Health Organization (WHO). Switzerland. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - "Laat mensen blijven en AIDS verdwijnen." AIDS Fonds. The Netherlands. (Female Version)., ca 1998. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - "Laat mensen blijven en AIDS verdwijnen." AIDS Fonds. The Netherlands. (Male Version)., ca. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 13)
      - "Bewusst Leben." Deutsche AIDS Holfe e.v. Germany. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 14)
      - "Als niemand luistert naar niemand vallen er doden in plaats van woorden." Amnesty International. Amsterdam, the Netherlands. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 15)
      - "Doe wat je wilt, doe het ret/Feel comfortable, use a condom." Multiple languages. Antwerp en productie SDR en CG & GD Amsterdam. The Netherlands., ca. 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 16)
      - "Safe Sex: Gerust doen." The Netherlands. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 17)
      - "AIDS – Linien er for alle." Danish Language. Collage-style illustrated poster. Denmark., ca. 1990s. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 18)
      - "AIDS Linien." Flattened pamphlet (double-sided). English and Danish Language. Facts about the AIDS Hotline in Copenhagen. Copenhagen, Denmark. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 19)
      - "Hot Rubber the Condom: To be, or not to be." Three naked men with fig leaves over genitals, posing as if on stage. Red tone over b/w. Advertisement for Hot Rubber Company, Zurich, Switzerland. (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 20)
      - "Schenk ihm Freude." Photo of gift boxes with naked men's buttocks on top of another man. Advertisement for the Hot Rubber Company Condom and Lubricant. © STOP AIDS. Zurich, Switzerland. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 21)
      - "Wer uber Nacht bliebt…" Close up of hot rubber condom in rear pocket of man wearing jeans, next to white toothbrush. Advertisement for the Hot Rubber Company, Zurich/Berlin. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Africa/North Africa (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - "Funding A Woman's Movement Against Sexual Violence in the Democratic Republic of Congo.", 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - "AIDS! You are capable of protecting yourself." STD/AIDS Control Programme, Ministry of Health, Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - "What have you heard about AIDS? " Uganda School Health kit on AIDS Control (Item 3). Ministry of Education, Ministry of Health (AIDS Control Programme). Unicef, Kampala. Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - "Care for People with AIDS." Uganda School Health kit on AIDS Control (Item 10). Ministry of Education, Ministry of Health (AIDS Control Programme). Unicef, Kampala. Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - " What does a person with AIDS look like?" English Language. Uganda School Health kit on AIDS Control (Item 6). Ministry of Education, Ministry of Health (AIDS Control Programme). Unicef, Kampala. Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - " Utamtambuaje Mtu Mwenye Ukimwi?" Swahili Language version of E7:04: 05. Uganda School Health kit on AIDS Control (Item 3). Ministry of Education, Ministry of Health (AIDS Control Programme). Unicef, Kampala. Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - "Prevent AIDS." English Language. Uganda School Health kit on AIDS Control (Item 9). Ministry of Education, Ministry of Health (AIDS Control Programme). Unicef, Kampala. Uganda., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - "Children have the right to live free from fear." Swahili/ English Language, (double-sided) Tanzania?, ca. 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - "Watoto wa mitaani, Wajibu wa nani?" Swahili/English Language. Mwanga, Tanzania. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 9)
      - "Haki za wasichana Kwanza; Girls Rights First." Swahili/English Language. Kuleana, Calendar. Mwanza, Tanzania., ca. 1996. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - "Kituo cha kutetea hakiza watoto/ Center for Children's rights." Swahili/English Language. Kuleana, Calendar. Mwanza, Tanzania., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 11)
      - "Sababu 100 za kumpongeza mtoto wako." Swahili Language. Kuleana, Center for Children's Rights. Mwanga, Tanzania, 1998. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 12)
      - "Unissons nos efforts contre le SIDA." French/Arabic? Language. Society Maghrebire de Recherche et de lute contre le SIDA. Institut Pasteur du Maroc. Casablanca, Morocco. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 13)
      - "8th International Conference on AIDS in Africa/8th African Conference on STDs." Palais des Congres. Marrakesh, Morocco., ca. December 12 – 17, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 14)
      - "Stop AIDS Now." Community AIDS information & Support Centre, Johannesburg City Health AIDS Prevention Programme. South Africa., ca. 1993. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 15)
      - "No AIDS Please: The Family Needs You." Federal Ministry of Health, Nigeria., ca. 1992. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 16)
      - "Join Nigeria in the Fight against AIDS." Federal Ministry of Health, Nigeria. National Oil & Chemical Marketing Company Ltd. Nigeria., ca. 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 17)
      - "Say No to Drugs." The Sierra Leone Ports Authority, Issued by- The Public Affairs Division of the National Council for the prevention of Alcoholism & Drug Dependency. Sierra Leone. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 18)
      - "The Sad End of Drug Abuse." United Nations International Drug Control Programme (UNDCP), National Council for the Prevention of Alcoholism & Drug Dependency. British High Commission Freetown, Sierra Leone. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 19)
      - "Principios oreintadones somber el VIH & El SIDA." Spanish Language. PNVD/UNCP. USA/Senegal. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 20)
      - "Principes directeurs relatifs au VIH & au SIDA." French Language. PNVD/UNCP. USA/Senegal. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 21)
      - "Stop AIDS in School." Hebrew Language. Jerusalem AIDS Project, The Association for Prevention of AIDS in Israel. Jerusalem, Israel. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 22)
      - "Control of Malaria." English Language. Produced by the Malaria Control Centre in conjunction with the Health Learning Materials Project. Ministry of Health. Funded by the World Health Organization. Lusaka, Zambia., ca. March 1992. (Box 7, Folder 5, Item 23)
    - India, Bangladesh, Nepal (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - January 2001 Calendar, original poster from Sight and Life. Helpless Rehabilitation Society. Kathmandu, Nepal., ca. January 2001. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Nepalese man thinking. Color illustrated poster. Nepalese Language. Nepal. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Happy couple with condom. Color illustrated poster. STD HIV AIDS, Funded by USAIDS. Possibly Nepal or Bangladesh., ca. 1997. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - "AIDS can happen to you: Protect yourself. " Bengali Language. AIDS Awareness foundation – AAF. Dhaka, Bangladesh. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - "No to Drugs, Yes to Life." English/Bengali Language. Voluntary Organization for the Needy-von. Manikqonj, Bangladesh. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - "AIDS: Sharing and care can protect the human race." English Language. Voluntary Organization for the Needy-von. Manikqonj, Bangladesh. 1997., ca. 1997. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - "Empower Migrant Workers Against HIV/AIDS." English Language. Caram-Asia (Coordination of Action research on AIDS and Mobility – ASIA). Kuala Lampur, India. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - "Healthy Youth, Healthy Nation, Prevent AIDS, Save Youth." St. Paul's Trust (AIDS Control Foundation of India. Samalkot, India, 1998., ca. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - "Risk of your getting HIV Infection is very low (45 – 120 times less than Hepatitis B). Even then, why take the risk?". AIDS Control Foundation of India (ACFI), St. Paul's Trust. Samalkot, India., ca. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - "Modified Guidelines for M.D.T. to be followed under N.L.E.P. (National Leprosy Elimination Program). " English and another language. H.K.N.S./St. Paul's Trust, MRO Office. Samalkot, India., ca. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - "ACFI 1998 Year Planner". AIDS Free India/St. Paul's Trust. Samalkot, India., ca. 1998. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - "Calendar 1995". DIPS Communication Centre. Orissa, India., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - "HIV/AIDS Does Not Spread This Way!" Tamilnadu State Control Society. Madras, India, ca. 1997. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - " HIV/AIDS Can Be Prevented This Way!" Tamilnadu State Control Society. Madras, India, 1997., ca. 1997. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Indian Preventative poster for healthcare workers. Indian Language. SIRMCE. India. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 15)
      - Doctor holding condom poster. Tamil Language. India. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Illustrated poster of heart with people, condom. Tamil Language. India. (Box 7, Folder 6, Item 17)
    - Asia, South Pacific, Australia, New Zealand, Russia (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - "Asian Pacific Islander American Health Forum – 2005 Annual Report." Asian and Pacific Islander American Health Forum, San Francisco/Washington D.C., ca. 2005. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - "OPIS Dewa ou." Indonesian Language. Program AIDS Peduli. (Double-sided, four-fold large poster). Jakarta, Indonesia., ca. 1992-3. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - "AIDS Does not Respect Tradition, Culture, or Religion." South Pacific Commission. Produced by the Pacific Islands AIDS and STD Prevention Programme. Funded by USAID and AUSAID. Auckland, New Zealand, 1995., ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - "Love with Care…A Community Commitment. Prevent AIDS." Produced by the Pacific Islands AIDS and STD Prevention Programme. Funded by the World Health Organization, USAID and AISAID. Auckland, New Zealand., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - "We are Professional About Preventing AIDS. Are You? " Produced by the New Zealand Prostitutes Collective (NZPC). Wellington/Auckland/Christchurch, New Zealand. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - "Map of Countries with HIV/AIDS, 1993". Compiled and drawn by the Division of National Mapping, Department of Resources and Energy, Canberra, Australia. Produced by the Pacific Islands AIDS & STD Prevention Programme. (PIASPP), South Pacific Commission. Auckland, New Zealand. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - "The Third National Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Health Worker's Conference. " Cairns, October 18-20, 1999. Aboriginal & Islander Health Worker Journal/Commonwealth Department of Health and Aged Care. Cairns, Australia. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - "Quanto maior a ignorancia, maior o risco." Chinese and Portuguese Language. Nao a SIDA, sim a vida. Unidade de educao para saude. Macao., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - "Nao partilhe aguihas nem seringas." Chinese and Portuguese Language. Nao a SIDA, sim a vida. Unidade de educao para saude. Macao., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - "Nao Deixe a sedisao Para os outros." Chinese and Portuguese Language. Nao a SIDA, sim a vida. Unidade de educao para saude. Macao., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - "AIDSED Centre 1991 Calendar." World Health Organization, Unesco AIDS Education and Health Promotion Materials Exchange Centre. UNESCO PROAP. Bangkok, Thailand. (2 copies). (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Illustrated poster of Russian villain with couple, condom. Russian Language. Infoshare International. Russia., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - "It's your Life. Love Carefully." New Zealand AIDS Foundation. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - "Love Carefully." Photo by Albert Sword. New Zealand AIDS Foundation. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - "Food for Thought." Photo by Albert Sword. New Zealand AIDS Foundation. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - "You Won't Believe What We Like to Wear in Bed." Photo by Albert Sword. New Zealand AIDS Foundation. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - "You'll Never forget the feeling of Safe Sex." AIDS Council, New South Wales/Victoria/Queensland/South Australia/Western Australia (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 17)
    - South America/Spanish Language, 1980s - 2000s (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. En donde se aloja el virus del SIDA." Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, grey version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Puedo contraer sida si al quien esternuda a tose cerca de mi?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, pink version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Me puedo contagiar de SIDA por un abrazo, un beso o por dar la mano?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, black version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Donde puedo obtener informacion sobre el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, black version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Puedo contraer SIDA a traves de alimentos platos o cubiertos?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, olive green version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Es Curable el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, grey version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Puedo contraer SIDA en los banos publicos oen un balneario?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, green version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Hay Peligro de que me infecte de SIDA sime sacan sangre?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, blue version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Quienes se pueden contagiar de SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, teal version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Como aumenta el riergo de contagion por el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, orange version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Que es el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, red version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Puedo contraer SIDA a traves de la Convivencia con pessonas infectadas?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, white version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Por que el condon disminuye el rissgo de contraer el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, lavender version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - "Barajamela mas despacio. Como se contagion el SIDA?" Illustrated poster of hand holding cards, yellow version. CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - "Sexo mas Seguro." Corporacio Chilena deprevencion del SIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - "Nuestra major arma contra el SIDA es la prevencion." CONSIDA. Chile. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - "Tu vida es segun el color…con que mires el SIDA." Condom, man in leather, sunglasses, green color. CONSIDA. Possibly Mexico. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - "En el diseno de tu vida…? Tomas en cuenta el SIDA? " CONSIDA. Comercia y Administracio Num. 35. Col. Copilco Universidad. Organge color, man with condoms. Possibly Mexico. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - "Como mujer, Estoy preparade." Spanish language. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - "El riesgo es de todos. El SIDA…si…da." CONSIDA. Spanish Language. Dirreccion general deepi demologica. Possibly Chile or Mexico. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - "Una llamade teletonica puede salvar tu vida." MHOL. Peru., 1995. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - "Ulacets. Conferencia Panamericana de SIDA." Lima, Peru., December 3 – 6 1997. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 22)
      - "Protejamos nuestro amor." Via Libre, Asociacion de lucha contra el SDA. Lima, Peru, 1995., ca 1995. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 23)
      - "Protejamos nuestro amor. Recomendacions para prevenir el SIDA." Via Libre, Asociacion de lucha contra el SDA. Lima, Peru, ca 1995. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 24)
      - "Protejamos nuestro amor. Conversemos en pareja." Via Libre, Asociacion de lucha contra el SDA. Lima, Peru, ca. 1995. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 25)
      - "Si Da. No Da. No cambies tu vida por el SIDA." Ministerio de sanidad y consume. Spanish Language., ca. 1987. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 26)
      - "Te quiero, te guido. Evitamos el SIDA." Centro nacional de educacion para la salud. Ministerio de salud publica, Cuba, ca. 1999. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 27)
      - "Que les espera en el future?" Con nuestro agradecimiento a la Cruz Roja Colombiana, Seccional Caldas. American Red Cross. Colombia., ca. December 1999. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 28)
      - "Contra el SIDA sexo. Seguro y Protegido!" Taller Visual documentation, blue abstract illustration. Spanish Language. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 29)
      - "Contra el SIDA sexo. Seguro y Protegido!" Taller Visual documentation, two men hugging, orange color. Spanish Language. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 30)
      - "Quitate la venda." Possibly Mexico. Black., ca. 1992. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 31)
      - "Caras venmos SIDA no sabemos." Programa de prevencion del SIDA. FEMAP. Federacion Mexicana de Asociaciones privadas de planificacion Familiar. A.C. Juarez, Chihuahua, Mexico. Spanish Language. (Box 7, Folder 8, Item 32)
    - San Francisco/San Francisco Aids Foundation Oversize (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - "In The Right Hands, This Can Help Someone With AIDS," Shanti Project, 28" x 11" (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 1 - 2)
        - "In the right hands, this can help someone with AIDS." Shanti project, picnic basket version. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 1)
        - "In the right hands, this can help someone with AIDS." Shanti Project, vacuum cleaner version. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - "Don't Share," San Francisco Dept of Public Health – 2 copies, one mounted [28" x 11"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - "AIDS. Es logue usted hace, y no logue usted es." San Francisco AIDS Foundation placard. Spanish Language, 1 of 3 versions. [28" x 11"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - "AIDS." San Francisco AIDS Foundation placard. Chinese language, 2 of 3 versions. [28" x 11"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - "AIDS. It's what you do, not who you are." English language. San Francisco AIDS Foundation placard, 3 of 3 versions. [28" x 11"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 6)
      - "The moral majority, family values, right to life." San Francisco AIDS Foundation. Funded by the San Francisco Department of Public health, 100% campaign., ca. 1992. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 7)
      - "Be here for the cure. Get early treatment for HIV." © San Francisco AIDS Foundation. People living with HIV: Photographed by Annie Liebovitz., ca. 1993. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 8)
      - "AIDS Walk SF: A ten-kilometer fundraising walkathon." San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1991. (matted poster in frame)., ca. Sunday, July 21, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 9)
      - "One small candle may light a million. " 12th International AIDS Candlelight Memorial & Mobilization. Organized internationally by Mobilization against AIDS. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 10)
      - "Sex is good." San Francisco AIDS Foundation, San Francisco Department of Public Health. Photo: Warwick May. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 11)
      - "Be here for the cure. Get early treatment for HIV." San Francisco AIDS Foundation. San Francisco Department of Public Health., ca. 1992. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 12)
      - "Life, Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness." © San Francisco AIDS Foundation & Haight Ashbury Free Clinics. Photo: Warwick May. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 13)
      - "Speed and you." Illustrated posted of a rocket moving towards dog face illustration. San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office. Art by Baseman, numbered 4/100. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 14)
      - "Speed: It will eat you alive." Illustrated poster of man with tail being eaten by man-faced animals. San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office. Art by Noe Bertha? Numbered 3/100. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 15)
      - "Don't Fuck with A User, Unless He's Hooked on Condoms". © San Francisco AIDS Foundation., ca. 1989. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 16)
      - "AIDS & Comfort II. An evening of culinary and performing arts to benefit Bay Area Service organizations.", ca. September 22, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 17)
      - "Do the right thing every time!" San Francisco General Hospital. Design by Jos. Sances. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 18)
      - Shrink-wrapped poster of Robert Spotorno, with an obituary from San Francisco AIDS Francisco AIDS Hotline Volunteer Publication. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 19)